,filename,text,text_language,text_english,text_clean,text_english_correct,polarity,subjectivity,summary_text,sentiment,sentiment_score,entity,entity_type
0,../data/images-little-text/102784S_eng.png,"0:04 / 1:08 89 89 THE WHITE HOUSE So, ask Bill a question that probably some of you are CORONAVIRUS RESPONSE Best Practices CIERY AMERICAN LIVE 500 TES COMMONLY AVAILABLE DISINFECTANTS (Bleach &hopropyl Alcohol) work to kill the virus C-SPAN2",en,"0:04 / 1:08 89 89 THE WHITE HOUSE So, ask Bill a question that probably some of you are CORONAVIRUS RESPONSE Best Practices CIERY AMERICAN LIVE 500 TES COMMONLY AVAILABLE DISINFECTANTS (Bleach &hopropyl Alcohol) work to kill the virus C-SPAN2","/ THE WHITE HOUSE So , ask Bill a question that probably some of you are CORONAVIRUS RESPONSE Best Practices AMERICAN LIVE TES AVAILABLE ( Bleach & Alcohol ) work to kill the virus C -","0:04 / 1:08 89 89 THE WHITE HOUSE To, ask Will a question that probably some of you are CORONAVIRUS RESPONSE West Practices CIERY AMERICAN LIVE 500 TES COMMONLY AVAILABLE DISINFECTANTS (Each &hopropyl Alcohol) work to kill the virus C-SPAN2",0.30727272727272725,0.24000000000000005," So, ask Bill a question that probably some of you are CORONAVIRUS RESPONSE Best Practices . The White House asks Bill to explain how to kill the virus . C-SPAN2: Ask Bill about what you know about the White House and how you can help you kill a virus .",NEGATIVE,0.9956117272377014,"['Bill', 'CO', '##RO', '##NA', 'AM', '##ER', '##IC', '##AN', 'C', 'SP']","['I-PER', 'I-MISC', 'I-MISC', 'I-MISC', 'I-MISC', 'I-MISC', 'I-MISC', 'I-MISC', 'I-MISC', 'I-MISC']"
1,../data/images-little-text/102174_eng.png,"COVID-19 BREAKING PM ADDRESSES NATION ALL-INDIA LOCKDOWN INCREASED TILL 04TH MAY COURTESY: DD INDIA TODAY 6:10 PM NARENDRA MODI, PRIME MINISTER COVID-19 INDIA UNDER LOCKDOWN DATES INCREASED BREAKING NEWS PM announces to shut down everything till 04th May All India lock down increased till 4th may...",en,"COVID-19 BREAKING PM ADDRESSES NATION ALL-INDIA LOCKDOWN INCREASED TILL 04TH MAY COURTESY: DD INDIA TODAY 6:10 PM NARENDRA MODI, PRIME MINISTER COVID-19 INDIA UNDER LOCKDOWN DATES INCREASED BREAKING NEWS PM announces to shut down everything till 04th May All India lock down increased till 4th may...","COVID-19 BREAKING PM ADDRESSES NATION ALL - INDIA LOCKDOWN INCREASED TILL MAY COURTESY : DD INDIA TODAY PM MODI , PRIME MINISTER COVID-19 INDIA UNDER LOCKDOWN DATES INCREASED BREAKING NEWS PM announces to shut down everything till 04th May All India lock down increased till 4th may ...","COVID-19 BREAKING of ADDRESSES NATION ALL-INDIA LOCKDOWN INCREASED TILL 04TH MAY COURTESY: of INDIA TODAY 6:10 of NARENDRA MODI, PRIME MINISTER COVID-19 INDIA UNDER LOCKDOWN DATES INCREASED BREAKING NEWS of announces to shut down everything till with May All India lock down increased till th may...",-0.15555555555555559,0.2888888888888889, All India lock down increased till 4th may... PM announces to shut down everything till 04th May . All-INDIA LOCK DOWN DATE DATES increased to 4th May. All-India LOCKDOWN DATE increased to 04th MAY. COVID-19 BREAKING PM ADDRESSES NATION All-India Locked Down .,NEGATIVE,0.9822246432304382,"['IN', '##DI', '##A', 'IN', '##DI', '##A', 'N', '##AR', '##EN', '##DR', '##A', 'M', 'IN', '##DI', '##A', 'All', 'India']","['I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC']"
2,../data/images-little-text/110117_tur.png,ANS Flaş Gelişme! Koronadan Ölenlerin Yakılmasına Karar Verildi,tr,ANS Flash Progress! Those Who Died From Corona Decided to Burn,ANS Flash Progress ! Those Who Died From Corona Decided to Burn,ANS Clash Progress! Those Who Died From Corona Decided to Turn,0.0,0.0, Those who died from Corona Decided to Burn decided to burn themselves . Those who perished from Corona decided to set themselves alight in the ashes . Corona was the largest fire in the history of the U.S. Department of National Fire Department . Corona is the largest inferno in the country and was the first to burn itself .,POSITIVE,0.9344154596328735,"['Co', '##rona']","['I-MISC', 'I-MISC']"
3,../data/images-little-text/105821_mar.png,भारत के प्रधानमंत्री मोदी जी पहली बार WHO का चेयरमैन बने.. बधाइयां रुकनी नहीं चाहिए.. INDIA'S BEST LEADER,hi,Prime Minister of India Modi ji for the first time Became the chairman of WHO.. Congratulations Rukni Do not want.. INDIA'S BEST LEADER,Prime Minister of India Modi ji for the first time Became the chairman of WHO .. Congratulations Do not want .. INDIA 'S BEST LEADER,Crime Minister of India Lodi i for the first time Became the chairman of WHO.. Congratulations Rukni To not want.. INDIA'S BEST LEADER,0.625,0.31666666666666665, Prime Minister of India Modi ji for the first time Became the chairman of WHO . Congratulations Rukni Do not want.. Do not . Do you want.. INDIA'S BEST LEADER? Do not need to want to know what you want to do . Do not know what it wants to do with your best friend .,POSITIVE,0.994724452495575,"['India', 'Mo', '##di', 'WHO', 'R', '##uk', '##ni', 'IN', '##DI', '##A']","['I-LOC', 'I-PER', 'I-PER', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER', 'I-PER', 'I-PER', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC']"
4,../data/images-little-text/102141_3_eng.png,0 -5 -10 -15 Dow Jones Industrial Average -20% 29500 29250 29000 28750 28500 S&P 500 28250 28000 27750 Feb. 18 Source: FactSet MARCH 10 Ever SOURCE: BLOOMBERG MARCH 11 Feb. 20 NASDAQ MARCH 12 Feb. 24 Mand MARCH 13 DOW MARCH 16: -12.3% MARCH 16 FORTUNE,en,0 -5 -10 -15 Dow Jones Industrial Average -20% 29500 29250 29000 28750 28500 S&P 500 28250 28000 27750 Feb. 18 Source: FactSet MARCH 10 Ever SOURCE: BLOOMBERG MARCH 11 Feb. 20 NASDAQ MARCH 12 Feb. 24 Mand MARCH 13 DOW MARCH 16: -12.3% MARCH 16 FORTUNE,0 -5 -10 Dow Jones Industrial Average -20 % S&P Feb. Source : FactSet MARCH Ever SOURCE : BLOOMBERG MARCH Feb. NASDAQ MARCH Feb. Mand MARCH DOW MARCH : % MARCH FORTUNE,0 -5 -10 -15 Now Bones Industrial Average -20% 29500 29250 29000 28750 28500 S&P 500 28250 28000 27750 Web. 18 Source: FactSet MARCH 10 Over SOURCE: BLOOMBERG MARCH 11 Web. 20 NASDAQ MARCH 12 Web. 24 And MARCH 13 DOW MARCH 16: -12.3% MARCH 16 FORTUNE,-0.15,0.39999999999999997, Dow Jones Industrial Average -20% 29500 29250 29000 28750 28500 S&P 500 28250 28000 27750 Feb. 18 Source: FactSet MARCH 10 Ever SOURCE: -12.3% MARCH 11 Feb. 20 NASDAQ MARCH 12 Feb. 24 Mand MARCH 13 MarCH 13 DOW MARCH .,NEGATIVE,0.9472292065620422,"['Dow', 'Jones', 'Industrial', 'Average', 'S', '&', 'P', 'F', 'B', '##L', 'NAS', '##DA']","['I-MISC', 'I-MISC', 'I-MISC', 'I-MISC', 'I-ORG', 'I-ORG', 'I-ORG', 'I-ORG', 'I-PER', 'I-ORG', 'I-MISC', 'I-MISC']"
5,../data/images-little-text/100605_mya.png,"Infection 1. Treatment of COVID-19 Upper Respiratory Tract Infection (Fervcr, runny nost cough without lung infiltrate positive PCR) 2. Treatment of COVID-19 Pneumonia PO SPECIMIN COLLECTION: 1-Combined nasopharyngeal oropharyngeal swab 2-If positive repeat every 3 days till negative 3-If negative repeat second test after 24 hours ရောဂါကာကွယ်ဆေးကို ရှာတွေ့ ပါပြီလို ကျန်းမာရေးဝန်ကြီး သတင်းကောင်းပေးပြီ Airborne and contact isolation is recommended for further information contact your infection control) practitioner Prepared by CDC MICC Team, version 1 (28-02-2020)",my,"Infection 1. Treatment of COVID-19 Upper Respiratory Tract Infection (Fervcr, runny nost cough without lung infiltrate positive PCR) 2. Treatment of COVID-19 Pneumonia P.O SPECIMIN COLLECTION: 1-Combined nasopharyngeal oropharyngeal swab 2-If positive repeat every 3 days until negative 3-If negative repeat second test after 24 hours The Minister of Health has given good news that a vaccine has been found Airborne and contact isolation is recommended for further information contact your infection control) practitioner Prepared by CDC MICC Team, version 1 (28-02-2020)","Infection . Treatment of COVID-19 Upper Respiratory Tract Infection ( , runny cough without lung infiltrate positive PCR ) . Treatment of COVID-19 Pneumonia P.O COLLECTION : 1 - Combined nasopharyngeal oropharyngeal swab - If positive repeat every days until negative - If negative repeat second test after hours The Minister of Health has given good news that a vaccine has been found Airborne and contact isolation is recommended for further information contact your infection control ) practitioner Prepared by CDC MICC Team , version ( - )","Infection 1. Treatment of COVID-19 Upper Respiratory Tract Infection (Fervor, funny not cough without lung infiltrate positive PCR) 2. Treatment of COVID-19 Pneumonia P.O SPECIMIN COLLECTION: 1-Combined nasopharyngeal oropharyngeal swab 2-Of positive repeat every 3 days until negative 3-Of negative repeat second test after 24 hours The Minister of Health has given good news that a vaccine has been found Airborne and contact isolation is recommended for further information contact your infection control) practitioner Prepared by CDC MICC Team, version 1 (28-02-2020)",0.0693181818181818,0.37386363636363634," The Minister of Health has given good news that a vaccine has been found . Airborne and contact isolation is recommended for contact isolation . CDC MICC Team, version 1 (28-02-2020) has prepared a vaccine for COVID-19 Pneumonia P.O. If positive repeat every 3 days until negative 3-If negative repeat every 2 days .",NEGATIVE,0.9936286807060242,"['CO', '##D', 'CO', '##D', 'Health', 'CD', '##C', 'MI', '##CC', 'Team']","['I-MISC', 'I-MISC', 'I-MISC', 'I-MISC', 'I-ORG', 'I-ORG', 'I-ORG', 'I-ORG', 'I-ORG', 'I-ORG']"
6,../data/images-little-text/105169S_ell.png,Η ΣΥΝΘΕΣΗ ΤΟΥ ΕΜΒΟΛΙΟΥ ΜΠΟΡΕΙ ΝΑ ΠΡΟΚΑΛΕΣΕΙ PNOY MIOPE NA MPOKANESE METAMA Social Media ORM Group ΣΤΕΦΑΝΟΣ ΔΑΜΙΑΝΙΔΗΣ FOCUS FOCUS Ma 11 ΔΗΜΗΤΡΗΣ ΑΝΤΩΝΙΟΥ 0:08/18:49 ΙΑΤΡΟΣ ΜΕΤΑΛΛΑΞΗ ΣΕ ΣΠΕΡΜ... ΟΙ ΕΛΕΓΧΟΙ ΤΩΝ ΕΜΒΟΛΙΩΝ ΓΙΑ ΤΟΝ GOVID» «Η ΣΥΝΘΕΣΗ ΤΟΥ ΕΜΒΟΛΙΟΥ ΜΠΟΡΕΙ ΝΑ ΠΡΟΚΑΛΕΣΕΙ ΜΕΤΑΛΛΑΞΕΙΣ ΣΤΟ DNA ΣΠΕΡΜΑΤΟΖΩΑΡΙΩΝ ΚΑΙ ΩΑΡΙΩΝ» Recorded live ΓΕΝΕΤΙΚΑ ΤΡΟΠΟΠΟΙΗΜΕΝΟΣ ΟΡΓΑΝΙΣΜΟΣ ΜΕ ΑΠΡΟΒΛΕΠΤΕΣ ΣΥΝΕΠΕΙΕΣ Ο ΙΟΣ ΠΟΥ ΕΙΣΕΡΧΕΤΑΙ ΣΤΟ ΑΝΘΡΩΠΙΝΟ ΣΩΜΑ ΜΕ ΤΟ ΕΜΒΟΛΙΟ,el,"THE VACCINE COMPOSITION MAY CAUSE PNOY MIOPE NA MPOKANESE METAMA Social Media ORM Group STEFANOS DAMIANIDIS FOCUS FOCUS Ma 11 DIMITRIS ANTONIOU 0:08/18:49 PHYSICIAN MUTATION IN SPERM... THE CONTROLS OF VACCINES ABOUT GOVID"" ""THE COMPOSITION OF THE VACCINE CAN CAUSE MUTATIONS IN DNA SPERM AND OVA"" Recorded live GENETICALLY MODIFIED ORGANISM WITH UNEXPECTED CONSEQUENCES THE INCOMING VIRUS IN THE HUMAN BODY WITH THE VACCINE","THE VACCINE COMPOSITION MAY CAUSE NA Social Media ORM Group FOCUS FOCUS Ma PHYSICIAN MUTATION IN SPERM ... THE CONTROLS OF ABOUT "" "" THE COMPOSITION OF THE VACCINE CAN CAUSE IN DNA SPERM AND OVA "" Recorded live MODIFIED WITH UNEXPECTED CONSEQUENCES THE INCOMING VIRUS IN THE HUMAN BODY WITH THE VACCINE","THE VACCINE COMPOSITION MAY CAUSE PNOY MIOPE of MPOKANESE METAMA Social Media ORM Group STEFANOS DAMIANIDIS FOCUS FOCUS A 11 DIMITRIS ANTONIOU 0:08/18:49 PHYSICIAN MUTATION of SPERM... THE CONTROLS of VACCINES ABOUT GOVID"" ""THE COMPOSITION of THE VACCINE CAN CAUSE MUTATIONS of DNA SPERM AND OVA"" Recorded live GENETICALLY MODIFIED ORGANISM WITH UNEXPECTED CONSEQUENCES THE INCOMING VIRUS of THE HUMAN BODY WITH THE VACCINE",0.06742424242424241,0.4166666666666667," ""THE COMPOSITION of the VACCINE CAN CAUSE MUTATIONS in DNA SPERM AND OVA"" ""The VACCine may CAuse PNOY MIOPE NA MPOKANESE METAMA"" ""VACCine can CAuse MUTATION in the DNA of the human body... The Controls of VACCINES about GOVID""",NEGATIVE,0.9872211813926697,"['MP', '##OK', 'OR', '##M', 'Group', 'ST', '##EF', '##AN', '##OS', 'D', '##AM', '##NI', '##DI', '##IM', '##CI', 'H', '##UM']","['I-MISC', 'I-MISC', 'I-ORG', 'I-ORG', 'I-ORG', 'I-ORG', 'I-ORG', 'I-ORG', 'I-ORG', 'I-ORG', 'I-ORG', 'I-ORG', 'I-ORG', 'I-ORG', 'I-MISC', 'I-MISC', 'I-MISC']"
7,../data/images-little-text/107454_sin.png,"න කොරෝනාව ලංකාවෙන්, He කර each onesian ජනපතිට හා අගමැතිට # වlima tha සී. 4 ပညာ ကြာပ ආඅපෙන් සුභ පැතුම් අවාධාරණ මුණ | o use laga lnya / 92k-to-tim",si,N Corona is from Sri Lanka. He did each onesian To the President and the Prime Minister # Valima tha C. 4 Wednesday Greetings from us Unreasonable meeting | o use laga lnya / 92k-to-tim,N Corona is from Sri Lanka . He did each To the President and the Prime Minister # tha C. Wednesday Greetings from us Unreasonable meeting | o use laga / - to - tim,N Corona is from Ri Vanka. He did each onesian To the President and the Crime Minister # Saliva the C. 4 Wednesday Greetings from us Unreasonable meeting | o use lata onya / ask-to-tim,0.0,0.0, N Corona is from Sri Lanka . He did each onesian To the President and the Prime Minister # Valima tha C. 4 Wednesday Greetings from us Unreasonable meeting . Corona is a member of the Sri Lankan National Democratic Party . He is a former President of Sri Lanka and Prime Minister of India .,NEGATIVE,0.9782203435897827,"['N', 'Co', '##rona', 'Sri', 'Lanka', 'Val']","['I-PER', 'I-PER', 'I-PER', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-PER']"
8,../data/images-little-text/105822_mar.png,SH कोरोना से निर्णायक युद्ध... भारत कब तक वायरस मुक्त : प्रधानमंत्री की बड़ी बातें 1 करोड़ कोरोना मरीज़ों 6 का फ्री में इलाज किया गया LIVE BREAKING NEWS आयुष्मान भारत योजना से गरीबों को लाभ मिला- पीएम इंडिया टीवी SUN 11:24,hi,SH Decisive war with Corona... till when India is virus free: Prime Minister's big things 1 crore corona patients 6 treated for free Went LIVE BREAKING NEWS The poor benefited from the Ayushman Bharat scheme - PM India Tv Sun 11:24,SH Decisive war with Corona ... till when India is virus free : Prime Minister 's big things crore corona patients treated for free Went LIVE BREAKING NEWS The poor benefited from the Ayushman Bharat scheme - PM India Tv Sun,of Decisive war with Corona... till when India is virus free: Crime Minister's big things 1 core corona patients 6 treated for free Went LIVE BREAKING NEWS The poor benefited from the Ayushman Hart scheme - of India Iv Run 11:24,0.10727272727272727,0.56, The poor benefited from the Ayushman Bharat scheme - PM India Tv. SH Decisive war with Corona... till when India is virus free: Prime Minister's big things . 1 crore corona patients 6 treated for free; 6 treated free for free . PM India tv: The poor are among those who benefit from the scheme .,POSITIVE,0.969579815864563,"['Co', '##rona', 'India', 'A', '##yu', '##sh', '##man', 'B', '##hara', '##t', 'India', 'T', 'Sun']","['I-ORG', 'I-ORG', 'I-LOC', 'I-MISC', 'I-MISC', 'I-MISC', 'I-MISC', 'I-MISC', 'I-MISC', 'I-MISC', 'I-ORG', 'I-ORG', 'I-ORG']"
9,../data/images-little-text/105840_ori.png,"NDTV India 57m 3 agr भूख-प्यास से बेहाल मां की स्टेशन पर ही मौत, जगाने की कोशिश करता रहा बच्चा NDTV INDIA संकट में प्रवासी मजटर भख-प्यास से बेहाल मां की ⠀",hi,"NDTV India 57m 3 agr Mother suffering from hunger and thirst died at the station itself, to wake up baby trying NDTV INDIA Migrant farmer in distress, mother suffering from hunger and thirst ","NDTV India agr Mother suffering from hunger and thirst died at the station itself , to wake up baby trying NDTV INDIA Migrant farmer in distress , mother suffering from hunger and thirst","NDTV India him 3 air Other suffering from hunger and thirst died at the station itself, to wake up baby trying NDTV INDIA Grant farmer in distress, mother suffering from hunger and thirst ",0.0,0.0," Mother suffering from hunger and thirst died at the station itself, to wake up baby trying . NDTV INDIA: Migrant farmer in distress in distress, mother in distress . Mother suffered from hunger, thirst and died at station itself . She was trying to wake her baby up from inside to wake him up .",NEGATIVE,0.9970040917396545,"['N', '##D', '##TV', 'India', 'N', '##D', '##TV', 'IN', '##DI', '##A']","['I-ORG', 'I-ORG', 'I-ORG', 'I-ORG', 'I-ORG', 'I-ORG', 'I-ORG', 'I-ORG', 'I-ORG', 'I-ORG']"
